The conspiracy is real.
Wander is a thriller, crime, mystery film directed by April Mullen.
After getting hired to probe a suspicious death in the small town of Wander, a mentally unstable private investigator
becomes convinced the case is linked to the same 'conspiracy cover up' that caused the death of his daughter.
Arthur Bretnik, played by Aaron Eckhart.
Elsa Viceroy, played by Katheryn Winnick.
Shelley Luscomb, played by Heather Graham.
Jimmy Cleats, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Sherif Luis Santi, played by Raymond Cruz.
Nick Cassidy, played by Brendan Fehr.
Wander is a 2020 American thriller film directed by
April Mullen and written by Tim Doiron.
It stars Tommy Lee Jones, Aaron Eckhart, Katheryn
Winnick, Heather Graham, and Roger Dorman.
The story focuses on two conspiracy theorists and
their investigation of a murder.
Wander was released in the United States on December 4, 2020.
The film explores themes of small town, post-traumatic stress
disorder (ptsd), paranoia, new mexico, flashback.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.